yavli.com 2018-02-16

# Yavli | Take Full Control Over Your Sponsored Content

Yavli is a sponsored content discovery platform with a wide reach across the Internet via a large group of websites, applications and properties. We consider your personal privacy to be very important and have therefore provided this Privacy Policy so you have a clear understanding of what information we collect and how such information is used and stored. By using Yavli and its Services you consent to this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”). At any time and without notice to you, we may modify this Privacy Policy by posting a revised version of this Privacy Policy on our websites. Your use of our Services constitutes your unconditional and binding acceptance of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments, revisions, alterations, modifications and/or supplements that we make from time to time in accordance with the provisions of hereof. You should regularly review this Privacy Policy to keep sufficiently updated. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed to them in our Terms of Service.

Information Collection & Usage

Yavli collects information from you in two ways: information you give to us, and information that we gather from your use of our Service, each as more specifically described below. Such information is made up of “Personal Information” and “Non-Personal Information.”

“Personal Information” means information that you provide to us that personally identifies you, such as your first and last name, email address, physical address, telephone number, billing information, or social security number.

“Non-Personal Information” means information that does not specifically identify you.

Information you give to us

We collect information that you give to us. For example, if a portion of our Services require that you register with us and provide information in the course of such registration in order to receive certain features of our Services. Such registration may include your disclosure to us of Personal Information.

Information we gather from your use of our Services

We, like many websites and applications, collect information about what parts of our Services you use and how you use them. Information we may gather includes, but is not limited to:

Computer or browser information such as your system activity, the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our Services and/or the Yavli websites, the time and duration of your use of our Services and any queries, browser type, and browser language.

Device information such as your hardware model, operating system, operating system version, mobile device type, unique identifiers from your computer or mobile device, application download information, and/or IP address.

Location information such as your geolocation when you use our Services from a mobile device and/or mobile application. We may ask for you to manually provide precise location information or to enable your mobile device to send us precise location information.

Please see the Cookies and Web Beacons section below for more information regarding what cookies are and how you can manage them as part of your use of our Services. We may also use unique identifiers, Flash cookies, web beacons, web server log information, or other technologies to collect information about you. In addition to the information that we collect from you for our own Service, we may collect information from you for third parties for purposes such as ad targeting, optimization and reporting.

Our Information Use

We collect information from you and our other users to administer our business activities and to measure and improve our Services. Information is also used to fulfill your requests, conduct research, and develop new services and/or offer additional products and services to you and our other users. In addition, information collected from you and our other end-users may be used in aggregate form to, among other things, determine the total number of end-users who are using our Services, prepare utilization reports for our Publishers and Advertisers and other Partners (as defined below), diagnose and fix compatibility problems or other problems with our Services, and perform statistical analyses to enable us to build higher quality, more useful online services. We may use your information to process account transactions that you request or authorize, to make you aware of new or other services that we or our Partners offer, or to help conduct surveys to assess and improve our Services. We will also use the information collected from you to show advertising and promotions tailored to your interests. If you submit a request for information about Yavli through our Services, we may use your e-mail address to assist you with any issues you may have or to send you an e-mail that gives you the opportunity to elect to receive periodic e-mail alerts from Yavli regarding developments at the company or to offer you other promotions of ours or our Partners, subject to your right to opt out of such communications, except as otherwise provided herein.

We may also use your e-mail address to send you important notices. Because this information is important to your use of our Service, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

We may combine your Personal Information that we have with other information that we obtain from Publishers, Advertisers, business partners or other companies. We may also combine your Personal Information with Non-Personal Information. If we do so, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

In providing our Services to you, we may find it necessary or beneficial to share your information with our partners, including our Publishers, Advertisers, technology partners, and services and content partners (collectively, “Partners”) or allow such Partners to gather information directly from you.

Some of this information that you provide to us or our Partners may include your Personal Information. We may share your Personal Information with third parties in certain circumstances including the following situations:

  * Consent: We will share Personal Information with third-parties when we have your consent to do so.

  * Partners: We provide your Personal Information to Partners who work with us to provide our Services, or provide services outside of and/or unrelated to our Services. Our Services with which our Partners may assist us include among other things, communicating with you about new or existing Yavli or third-party services, creating or maintaining our databases, researching or analyzing our users, or processing payment card information.

  * Affiliates: We may share your Personal Information with any and all of our Affiliates. “Affiliates” means any entity controlled by, controlling, or under common control with Yavli. Our Affiliates will use and distribute your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

  * Legal Issues: Yavli will use your Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We will also use or share your Personal Information in order to prevent, or take action regarding any illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms or as otherwise required by law even without a subpoena, warrant, or court order.

  * Acquisition or Merger: If in the future we sell or transfer our assets or portions of our business, or if we experience a change in control, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer information to our successor or buyer, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

  * Public Postings; User Reviews: As noted in this Privacy Policy, we may store, display, sell, and/or transfer any comments or postings you make within public forums that we provide as part of the Services. If you voluntarily disclose Personal Information as part of such posting, that information may appear on our Services or we may sell or otherwise transfer that Personal Information to third-parties. Please be aware that such publicly-displayed information can also be collected and used by others without our control. We cannot control who reads your review or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily provide using the community services, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your Personal Information. The information presented in the public comment areas reflects the views of the individual users or hosts and does not necessarily reflect our views or the views of any of our Affiliates.

We reserve the right to share your Non-Personal Information publicly and with others. Examples of public information disclosures include providing anonymous reports to our Partners, such as the number of users who viewed advertising on our Services. In addition, some of the Non-Personal Information is provided to our Partners for uses such as calculating amounts owed by or to such Partners, or helping such Partners improve their services, amongst others.

Transfers of your information shall at all times be in accordance with applicable law. Yavli disclaims any liability or obligation as a result of any third party actions or omissions concerning your information, including those occurring as a result of our sharing and disclosure pursuant to this Privacy Policy. We urge you to contact third parties directly with any issues you may have concerning their use of your information. Please see Third-Party Practices below for more information on third-party use of your information.

Cookies and Web Beacons

When you visit our Services, a cookie that uniquely identifies your browser may be sent to your computer or mobile device. A “cookie” is a small file containing your preferences that is sent to your browser and sent back by your browser each time your browser accesses our servers. Cookies that we may use may only be read by the server that placed them there. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service (for example, by fulfilling your language, filtering and other preferences) and to better understand how people interact with our Services (for example, by tracking user trends and patterns of how people interact with advertising appearing within our Services). Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some aspects of the Services may not function properly without cookies. If you would like more information about cookies and how to control and delete cookies in various browsers, such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Opera and Chrome, please click here.

We currently or may in the future use the services of web analytics companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our Services, including the advertising on the Services. To do this, we allow the web analytics companies to include Web beacons and cookies on the web pages comprising part of the Services. The type of information collected via such Web beacons and cookies includes page content, page views, click-throughs by users, and other similar information. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like user preferences, popular search and content categories, click-through rates, how to improve our Services, and what kinds of offers our users like to see. Although our web analytics companies log this information on our behalf, we control how that data may be used.

Most, if not all, of the advertisements appearing on the Services are delivered to you by us or one of our Advertisers. In the course of delivering such advertisements, we or our Advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, or place web beacons, JavaScript or other similar technologies on our Services for the purpose of collecting information. Thereafter, information about your visits to the Services, such as the number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other Personal Information), is used to deliver targeted advertisements to you, a practice commonly known as “behavioral advertising.” The information collected by our Advertisers through cookies, web beacons or other similar technologies is anonymous, and our Advertisers are not authorized to collect any Personal Information about you. For more information about cookies please click here. To "opt-out" of receiving cookies from certain of our Advertisers, please click here.

Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personal Information

If you have an account with us, you have the ability to review and update your Personal Information online by clicking on the link to your account within the Services and logging into your account. You can also review and update your Personal Information by contacting us legal@yavli.com. Generally, we will not modify your Personal Information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your Personal Information if it changes or is inaccurate. Upon your request, we will close your Yavli Account and remove your Personal Information from view as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with applicable law. We do retain Personal Information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms, and take other actions permitted by law.

Confidentiality and Security

We recognize our responsibility to protect the Personal Information you entrust to us. We restrict access to Personal Information to Yavli employees, contractors, Affiliates, Partners (as described in this Privacy Policy), and agents. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law to guard your information. While we take precautions against possible breaches in our Services and customer databases, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. Your use of our Services is at your own risk. We urge you to take steps to protect your Personal Information when you are on the Internet by changing your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure Internet browser.

Third-Party Practices

When users access our Services, Non-Personal Information, such as IP addresses and search terms or phrases, is transmitted to certain Partners with whom Yavli has subcontracted so that those Partners can deliver responsive advertising, or other services and, in some cases, for the internal data reporting purposes of those Partners. Our Partners are obligated by applicable law to protect the privacy of certain types of data; however, we are not responsible for their actions or omissions, including the manner in which they use information that they receive from us. Nevertheless, if you feel that any of our Partners, or any third party who claims association with Yavli, is improperly collecting or using information about you, we urge you to contact them directly and also to inform us by e-mailing us at legal@yavli.com.

Certain of our Partners who provide or enable any functionality on the Services may also request or require that you download certain software or collect information from you, including Personal Information in order to access such functionality. We are not responsible for the contents of any software downloaded or the privacy practices of our Partners. In addition, any web sites that you click to from the Services may have been developed by third-parties over which we exercise no control. Such web sites may send their own cookies to end-users, collect data, or solicit Personal Information from you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including such web sites' use of any information collected when our end-users click through to such web sites. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a third party, we strongly encourage you to contact them directly or visit their individual web sites to learn more about their individual privacy policies.

Regarding Children

Children between the ages of 13 and 18

Our Services are not intended for people under the age of 18 and in accordance with our Terms, if you are under the age of 18 you are prohibited from using our Services.

COPPA

We comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). For more information about COPPA and children's privacy, please click here. When we use the term "parent" below, we mean to include legal guardians.

Children under the age of 13

Our Service is not directed to people under the age of 13. We do not provide memberships or accounts to persons under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may not give us any Personal Information, and you may not create an account register, sign up for or participate in any aspect of our Services. Except as may be required by law, we will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any Personal Information from children under the age of 13.

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors or end-users who are under the age of 13. If you believe that we have collected Personal Information about a visitor or end-user who is under the age of 13, please contact us at legal@yavli.com and such account and/or Personal Information will be deleted.

Information for Parents

We encourage parents to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the Internet, including our Services. Parents should regularly oversee their children's use of e-mail and other online communications and transactional features. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers that can help provide a safe online environment for kids.

Parents may request a review and/or removal of their child's Personal Information at any time by contacting us at legal@yavli.com. To protect the child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify the parent's identity before granting him or her access to the child's Personal Information.

Additional Terms

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Your continued use of our Services after such change has been made will signify your acceptance of such change.

California Privacy Rights Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits end users who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send us an e-mail at legal@yavli.com.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at legal@yavli.com.
